[{"answer": "Look, I think Rob Portman acted in a way that was consistent with the love for his son and also consistent with a movement that's happening across the country with Republican legislators.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Margaret, what did you make of that?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think it's obviously what he thinks is the right thing for his family.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "David Bossie, is what Senator Portman did a good thing or a bad thing?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, look, I have very small children, so I'm -- years --", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "So what would you do if one of your children came to you and said, \"Dad, I'm gay\"?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, we hope so, yes.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "They are going to grow up, right?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, you believe -- you may believe that people can be born gay.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "One second there you say do something wrong, would be the fact they were born gay be something they had done wrong?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "But you would try to correct the wrong, as you put it?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I would have advised Senator Portman to show unconditional love for his child but not -- not abandon his principles, which he has espoused the last many years.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "OK, what would you advise Senator Portman to do?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "So what I would offer David is a fourth consideration.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Margaret?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Just one second, I don't make decisions, I'll be candid with you, we don't make public policy decisions in the conservative moment based on what the latest poll says.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "At point will you move with the time?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, Piers, I hate to use your own tool against you, but you just cited polling.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "So, is that what this is all about?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Here is the problem, Mr. Bossie, to facilitate that logical extension of thought process, every single woman in America needs to walk around with a gun.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Let me just say this, do you think, Piers, it would bad thing for all potential rapists to think the woman they are about to rape would be armed and wouldn't bad way to stop a potential rape?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "A rapist has to think that the woman may be armed that's all it takes.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "How do they know when they're going to rape?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "They do know if you disarm everyone in America, they do know you are not armed.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How do they know when they are going to be attacked by a rapist?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, it doesn't there are criminals and there are people who obviously, Piers, violate 30 or 40 federal laws long before they murder somebody.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "That seems to fly in the face of your argument?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life before you met Rita?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "That's very good question.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "In terms of the defense, how are they positioning the defense now, in light of what these witnesses have been saying?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "There were allegations in town there could possibly be a cover-up, the media wasn't providing much coverage about the case, and so, I wrote about it.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Why do you care so passionately about this case?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "I think it's very important, Piers, that the two witnesses testified that they actually saw both defendants involved in digital penetration of this young woman's vagina, which is rape --", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What do you think of the developments in the last 24 hours?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, you can't blame an entire town for what a bunch of kids did.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How significant do you think that aspect to this case is, the fact that these two are star football players in a town that's football crazy?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "No, because it's natural.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "NTERVIEWER: You weren't thinking that a girl who keeps repeatedly throwing up was pretty drunk?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "You see that a lot?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Not just at parties.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "At parties?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes, you can see that anywhere.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "People throwing up because they had too much to drink?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, the defense, of course, is trying to pierce holes in the issue of whether or not she was drunk.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "But in terms what they said there about a culture of drunkenness and so on, could that play against this girl in the sense she got so drunk, a variety of parties that she didn't know what was going on?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I'm gonna put you on the stand.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "So, what do we do now?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "It means they get to tear you apart.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "I get to tell my story?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I believe that is a dramatization.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "So, you know, they would argue, I guess, well, look, both sides don't agree because it is a dramatization?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I think it was a week or two, as I remember.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "How long was it before he finally told you?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'm almost 74.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Where do you feel you get the strength to be like this?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "But let's, Valerie, take a break.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "What could be better?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I'm serious.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness, my husband telling me that he thought we should adopt.", "docId": "130315pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "If I could replay a moment for you now, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 509}]